We also come here and from style I can say that I want
What do I want?
Let's leave it empty right for now and over here. We have image
We also have video or flow state button right now what we want is image and it says you're currently on a free plan upgrade
Yes
You still have yet to make your first
AI image generation, please type a prompt above to create your first image set. Yes, so I click on generate and
I wait
Validation field, please check your request parameters
I think I have to specify a style. So I set it on none and I click on generate again
Yes
But as you see it's already removed the tokens from me right so it takes 40 tokens and it has removed them
For the very prompt that didn't even work, but whatever
I'm waiting
For none of banana to generate my image
And as you see, this is what we have as the image generated for us
so it's pretty beautiful, you know, and we can
download the image